

CONTACT

🔀 n.gihming@yahoo.com



+6010-5159602



Penang, Malaysia



www.linkedin.com/in/gihmingng

SKILLS

Professional

Photography and Videography

Video and photo editing

Graphic/UI designing

Slides designing

Enthusiatics

3D Modelling

LANGUAGE

English

Chinese

Malay

NG GIH MING

Software Engineer Student

in University of Malaya

SUMMARY

Like to involve myself in all kinds of activities ranging from volunteering jobs and organisation's committee. An easy-going person and willing to make new friends. Have about 4 years of experience in graphic designing and skilled in Adobe's apps as well. Some of the designing stuffs that I have done are designing shirt, posters, banners, animated PowerPoint slides and 3D modelling as well. Also interested in programming, photography and videography.

EXPERIENCE

Apprentices of ICMS Embark Program

Dec 2021

A 1-week internship program exposing real-world jobs scope to undergraduate

Responsible for designing a HRIS apps for Sunway Successfully make a HRIS app in 1 week starting from formulating an idea. deciding the function, choosing the best prototype and designing the front-end of the app.

Production of Graduation MV College

Mar 2021 - May 2021

Position held: Director, Editor, Videographer, Screenwriter

Apply skills learnt (Editing skills and screenwriting) in producing this memorable MV for all graduates to portray the lifestyle of matriculation students.

Involved in whole production of MV at the same time preparing for final exam.

Development of School Timetable System

Dec 2021 - Jan 2022

Done a timetable register system for school

Use Java to develope a timetable register desktop app for staffs as well as students while implement MySQL, JavaFx as UI to develope this sem 1 project.

Programming League Nation 2022

Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

Position held: Multimedia Creation

Hackathon competition that targets undergraduates in Malaysia. Responsible for editing social media post, posters and backdrop.

EDUCATION

University of Malaya

Oct 2020 - present

Major: Software Engineer

Kedah Matriculation College

Feb 2019 - Apr 2021

Field: Physical Science